<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE workshop>
<workshop month="11月" place="ハイブリッド（東京＆オンライン）">

<summary>
  <title>CALL FOR PAPERS (Deadline Extended to September 7, 2022)</title>
  <FstLine>the 19th International Workshop of</FstLine>
  <SndLine>Logic and Engineering of</SndLine>
  <TrdLine>Natural Language Semantics 19</TrdLine>
  <short>LENLS19</short>
  <site>
    <name>Hybrid (Online | The University of Tokyo, Komaba 1 Campus)</name>
    <address>3-8-1 Komaba, Meguro-ku, Tokyo (zip:153-8902)</address>
    <url>https://www.c.u-tokyo.ac.jp/eng_site/</url>
  </site>
  <conferencedate>November 19(Sat), 20(Sun), and 21(Mon), 2022</conferencedate>
  <email>lenls19[[at]]easychair.org</email>
  <website>https://lenls.github.io/lenls19/</website>
  <isbn></isbn>

  <invitedspeaker name="Michael Moortgat" affiliation="Utrecht University" />
  <invitedspeaker name="Kohei Kishida" affiliation="University of Illinois" />
  <invitedspeaker name="Nayuta Miki" affiliation="Osaka Universty" />
  <!--invitedspeaker name="Matthew Gotham" affiliation="University of Oxford" /-->
</summary>

<description><p>LENLS is an annual international conference on formal linguistics (i.e., syntax, semantics 
and pragmatics), computational linguistics, and the philosophy of language.  We are happy 
to announce that from this year, LENLS will be held under the umbrella of <host url="http://www.folli.info/">The Association 
for Logic, Language and Information (FoLLI)</host>.</p>

<p>LENLS19 is scheduled to take place in a hybrid format, that is, with both a physical presence 
option in Tokyo and a virtual presence option via zoom, while monitoring the global COVID-19 pandemic. </p></description>

<call>
We welcome submissions on topics in formal linguistics (syntax, semantics, pragmatics), computational 
linguistics, the philosophy of language, and related fields, including but not limited to the following:
</call><topics>
<topic>Formal syntax, semantics and pragmatics of natural language</topic>
<topic>Model-theoretic and/or proof-theoretic semantics of natural language</topic>
<topic>Computational approaches to semantics and pragmatics</topic>
<topic>Nonclassical logic and its relation to natural language (especially substructural, fuzzy, categorical, 
and topological logic)</topic>
<topic>Formal philosophy of language</topic>
<topic>Scientific methodology and/or experimental design in linguistics</topic>
</topics>

<submission>
Authors are required to choose from one of the following two submission categories: <category>Abstract Only</category>
and <category>Abstract+Full Paper</category>.  For both categories, authors must submit abstracts (anonymous, 
up to 4 pages including figures and references, A4 size, 12-point font) on original, 
unpublished research.  Abstracts must be submitted electronically in PDF at:

<url>https://easychair.org/conferences/?conf=lenls19</url>

<p>Upon acceptance, authors (both categories) are expected to submit extended 
abstracts (up to 5 pages) before the workshop.  Note that abstracts submitted to the <category>Abstract+Full Paper</category> 
category may be accepted in the <category>Abstract Only</category> category (but not vice versa).  The proceedings of 
the workshop will be made available online, including extended abstracts (both categories).</p>

<p>Authors submitting to the <category>Abstract+Full Paper</category> category are required to submit a full paper (up to 14 pages) 
for the post-proceedings volume after the conference and must agree to review at least one other full 
paper.</p>
</submission><!--selectedpaper /-->

<importantdates>
<importantdate name="Abstract submission deadline"     date="Wed, Sep. 7, 2022 (extended)" done="yes" />
<importantdate name="Notification of acceptance"       date="Sat, Oct. 1, 2022" />
<importantdate name="Deadline for camera-ready abstracts"   date="End of October 2022"  />
<!--importantdate name="Deadline for early registration" date="Nov. 1, 2022" /-->
<importantdate name="LENLS19"                          date="Nov. 19-21, 2022" />
<importantdate name="Deadline for full papers"         date="End of December 2022"  />
</importantdates><!--registration /--><!--program--><!--tutorial/--><!--sponsor/-->

<code>
<cp>All attendees, speakers, sponsors and volunteers at our conference are required to adhire to the following code of conduct. Organisers will enforce this code throughout the event. We expect cooperation from all participants to help ensure a safe environment for everyone.</cp>
<ct>The Quick Version</ct>
<cp>The organizers are dedicated to providing a harassment-free conference experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, or religion (or lack thereof). We do not tolerate harassment of conference participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any conference venue, including talks, workshops, parties, and social media. Conference participants violating these rules may be sanctioned or expelled from the conference without a refund at the discretion of the organisers.</cp>
<ct>The Less Quick Version</ct>
<cp>Harassment includes offensive verbal comments related to gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, and religion (or lack thereof), as well as sexual images in public spaces, deliberate intimidation, stalking, following, harassing photography or recording, sustained disruption of talks or other events, inappropriate physical contact, and unwelcome sexual attention.</cp>
<cp>Participants asked to stop harassing behavior are expected to comply immediately.</cp>
<cp>If a participant engages in harassing behavior, the conference organisers may take any action they deem appropriate, including warning the offender or expulsion from the conference without a refund.</cp>
<cp>If you experience harassment, notice that someone else is being harassed, or have any other concerns, please contact the following conference staff members immediately: Elin McCready and Daisuke Bekki</cp>
<cp>THe conference staff will be happy to help participants contact hotel/venue security or local law enforcement, provide escorts, or otherwise assist those experiencing harassment to feel safe for the duration of the conference. We value your attendance.</cp>
<cp>We expect participants to follow these rules at conference and workshop venues as well as conference-related social events.</cp>
</code>

<pcmembers>
  <pcmember name="Daisuke Bekki"       affiliation="Ochanomizu University"         role="chair" />
  <pcmember name="Alastair Butler"     affiliation="Hirosaki University" />
  <!--pcmember name="Richard Dietz"       affiliation="University of Tokyo" /-->
  <!--pcmember name="Patrick D. Elliott"  affiliation="Massachusetts Institute of Technology" /-->
  <pcmember name="Naoya Fujikawa"      affiliation="University of Tokyo" />
  <pcmember name="Yurie Hara"          affiliation="Hokkaido University" />
  <pcmember name="Robert Henderson"    affiliation="University of Arizona" />
  <pcmember name="Hitomi Hirayama"     affiliation="Keio University" />
  <pcmember name="Magdalena Kaufmann"  affiliation="University of Connecticut" />
  <!--pcmember name="Kristina Liefke"     affiliation="Ruhr University Bochum" /-->
  <pcmember name="Koji Mineshima"      affiliation="Keio University"               role="cochair" />
  <pcmember name="Elin McCready"       affiliation="Aoyama Gakuin University"      role="cochair" />
  <pcmember name="Yoshiki Mori"        affiliation="University of Tokyo" />
  <pcmember name="David Y. Oshima"     affiliation="Nagoya University" />
  <pcmember name="Katsuhiko Sano"      affiliation="Hokkaido University" />
  <pcmember name="Osamu Sawada"        affiliation="Kobe University" />
  <pcmember name="Ribeka Tanaka"       affiliation="Ochanomizu University" />
  <pcmember name="Wataru Uegaki"       affiliation="University of Edinburgh" />
  <pcmember name="Katsuhiko Yabushita" affiliation="Naruto University of Education" />
  <pcmember name="Tomoyuki Yamada"     affiliation="Hokkaido University" />
  <pcmember name="Shunsuke Yatabe"     affiliation="Ochanomizu University" />
  <pcmember name="Kei Yoshimoto"       affiliation="Tohoku University" />
</pcmembers>

<localorganizers>
  <localorganizer name="Yoshiki Mori"        affiliation="University of Tokyo" />
  <localorganizer name="Ribeka Tanaka"       affiliation="Ochanomizu University" />
  <localorganizer name="Yuta Takahashi"       affiliation="Ochanomizu University" />
</localorganizers>

</workshop>

